lala.com 2009-04-17

# Privacy Policy - Listen free on Lala

## Our Commitment to Privacy.

Welcome to la la. Our privacy policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our members. This policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our members' needs, so please refer back to it periodically. You will always find the latest version posted here. BY USING LA LA AND PROVIDING US WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRIVACY PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS POLICY STATEMENT. 

## Information Collection and Use.

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other services to you and prospective members. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. We use non-personally-identifiable information including IP addresses and aggregate user data to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track movement around the site and to gather demographic information about our membership base as a whole. 

If you choose to register with us we request certain basic information to enable us to provide you with our services. For example, we ask you to provide your name, age, mailing address, e-mail address, and credit card number. We store this information to save you time and allow for easier use of our services. We also look at the music you stream and have in your la la collection in order to help us provide you with better recommendations. 

In order to facilitate member interaction, we allow users to browse your la la collection and view feeds of what you are listening to. Additionally, we display your nickname and, if you've provided it, your image on our site, and we allow users to search for members by name, nickname or email address. Of course, the nature of our trading service requires disclosure of your name and mailing address to members who agree to ship you their CDs. 

You can invite friends to join la la by sending invitation e-mails via our automated invitation system. la la stores the e-mail addresses that you provide so that the respondents may be added to your friend's list, and also to send reminders of the invitations. la la does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and invitation reminders. Recipients of invitations may contact la la to request the removal of their information from our database. 

Similar to other commercial web sites, we utilize cookies and other technologies to collect non-personally-identifiable information about how our site is used. This data is used to enhance the functionality of our site and to make your transactions and other activities more convenient and efficient. 

Cookies are a feature of web browser software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a web site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by your web browser on your hard drive. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include information such as the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, and time spent at our site. Cookies can remember what information you accessed on one web page to streamline your transactions on related web pages. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set; however, you must enable cookies from la la in order to utilize the site. 

## Disclosure of Information to Strategic Partners.

la la takes your privacy very seriously. Be assured that la la does not sell or rent your contact information to marketers. However, there are times when it may be advantageous for la la to make certain personal information about you available to companies that we have a strategic relationship with or that perform work for us to provide products and services that we think will be of interest to you. 

## Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information.

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. 

## Web Blogs and Blurbs.

Please be aware that when you voluntarily post public information using our Blog and Blurb features, that information is visible to other members. la la is not responsible for personally identifiable information you choose to submit in our Blogs and Blurbs. 

## Security.

la la takes administrative, technical and physical precautions to protect the information that is stored within our database. We use industry standard (SSL) encryption technology to safeguard your credit card information while it is transmitted over the Internet, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note, however, that despite our reasonable precautions, unauthorized entry, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of your information at any time. 

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.

Our site and services are directed to the general public. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 years of age. 

## Contact Information.

If you have any questions or suggestions about this privacy statement, please contact us at support@lala.com.
